.
Woke up from a long bad dream The hollow sound
from a thin machine They try to break us, try to
tear us down They stole the signal, they stole
the crown It's a heart reset
We're starting over, no regrets It's a hard
reset
This is the sound we won't forget
We're wiping the slate clean A brand new
Stardust engine scene
This isn't rage, this is relief The sound of
finding our own peace This isn't stardust, this
is an engine This is the family we're defending
We're starting over, no regret It's a hard
reset, oh This is a sound we won't forget
We're wiping the slate clean A brand new start, a
standing scene
We are the cosmos. We are the fire. We're taking
this one higher and higher.
We are the Stardust
Engine.
It's a hard reset.
We're starting over, no regrets. It's a hard
reset.
This is a sound we won't forget.
We're wiping the slate clean. A brand new start,
us tangents in
it A heart reset
We're starting over, we're coming home